# Aleksandar Stojkovski

Bitola, Pelagonia, North Macedonia



astojkovski0@gmail.com



+38975735677



in linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-stojkovski-a6787a182

# **Summary**

There are three kinds of men: ones that learn by reading, a few who learn by observation, and the rest of them have to pee on the electric fence and find out for themselves! Without hesitation, I place myself in the last category every time. Regardless of the tasks I have for the day, I always try to find the hardest route which is also coincidentally the most rewarding one. In other words, nothing so far has been easy in my life so, why run from it and not just embrace it? (sorta like Batman).

Honesty, this part of the intro has been in my "about" section long before I started swimming in the waters of digital marketing. In fact, my failed attempt to get into the military was the biggest eye-opener that a guy can have. For quite a while, it was hard for me to find my place in the world let alone choose a career path that can make me fulfilled and well taken cared of financially.

Then, after the pandemic, the world of digital marketing caught my eye and I realized that I can use every single one of my skills and implement them into my job. Physical training is still a huge part of my life and takes a major portion of every single day, (especially on Sundays).

I like to lift weights and people's spirits. However, despite being a digital marketing specialist, I am an ultra runner with plenty of medals in the drawer (for now). Even if this sounds a bit salesy and goes against the regulations of making the perfect account here on Linkedin, I'd rather stay true to myself and leave some room for optimization later on.

Running on mountain tops with headphones while answering calls and constantly listening to podcasts is how I strive to improve in the digital marketing world. I'm always trying to understand the ideology of entrepreneurs, learn more about their mindset, and overall extract discipline which can successfully carry me through my day-today tasks.

Who says you can't chase a "high" while being a marketer? My experience with different audiences from all over the world has given me a unique perspective on creating digital solutions that are relevant for many businesses and best of all, they work!

# **Experience**



# Digital Marketing Specialist

BizzBee Solutions Feb 2023 - Present (3 months)



# Content Writer

**CLICKVISION Digital** 

Dec 2021 - Feb 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Being in an "I need to find myself" sort of life period, this job truly discovered my capabilities and made me boost my creativity. I think of myself as the opposite of a tea drinker that sits in a chair for 8 straight hours, but somehow this job made it easy. I work and focus on my tasks while listening to podcasts or music that inspire me to actually be a content writer and explain the things that are scattered all over the internet clearly so people can decide better on their purchase, regardless of the product. Without being too self-conscious, I stand behind every word that I write and always try to push the boundaries a little more by implementing my own personal interests into every article.

# f Graphic Designer

#### Fiverr

Jan 2010 - Feb 2023 (13 years 2 months)

As a high-schooler, I needed to help my family and earn a small income. I made T-shirt designs for people, vector logos, banners, and overall helped them have a unique piece of clothing. Fiverr was a great starting point that taught me to prioritize, communicate with people around the world, and develop a work ethic that I later on implemented in every single project that came my way. I familiarized myself with Photoshop and Gimp along the way and polished my skills every chance that I got.

# Customer Service Representative

#### Taskforce

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 (5 months)

This experience has taught me a lot. As a customer care representative, I worked for the largest and most challenging client, with more than 30 pediatricians and 62 clinics across the country. I was always on the line helping people make an appointment with their chosen doctor or get a prescription filled. I learned what it is like to work in a hybrid workplace. I can honestly say that my planning, adapting, and problem solving skills got quite and improvement. The multi-tasking part is something that I could always do so the company helped me polish it and become a more fluent and confident talker. I never shy away from a conversation which allowed me to show my skills to the people who are or will be providing my income.

The job was demanding, but nothing that I couldn't handle. The deal breaker was the working hours. I had to work from 5 pm until 1 am, which prevented me from spending quality time with the family.

# 🥷 Social Media Designer

#### Itcoderz

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Despite the fact everyone is on social media, only a small percentage of the population uses it as a source of income. I have always had a love-hate relationship with social media, but I can definitely make a product more appealing or, in this case, promote the products truthfully and exactly like they are.

I read a quote that inspired me to mix marketing and social media platforms to acquire some extra cash and work as a social media manager as a side hustle. There are two forms of content that receive attention on social media, educational content and entertaining content. Using that advice, I eliminated everything in between and used my Photoshop, Illustrator, Gimp, Excel, and WordPress skills to dab my pinky into a whole different career path.

# Content Creator

Pickatale - read, listen and learn! Jan 2016 - Nov 2021 (5 years 11 months) Before Covid 19, working from home was a rare privilege that, even for one second, I did not take for granted. Despite working as a freelancer, I got my hands on many projects for many years. So far, Pickatale was the work-wise the most important experience. I learned the fundamentals of time management, problem-solving, planning, multitasking, and much more. Along the way, a learned basic Swedish, Norwegian, and Danish. As the most optimistic person in any room that I enter, I took great pleasure in offering kids a new and innovative way to read books and learn new words. I was a content creator and a translator. Also, I edited audio tracks, which is very important because I was able to learn and understand the narrative much better.



### **Guitarist**

#### Dream

Jun 2007 - Nov 2020 (13 years 6 months)

When you are a small chubby kid, you are bound to turn on your rebellious side and buy a Metallica tshirt. Since I heard the intro to Enter Sandman, nothing was the same, and I immediately started to beg my parents for a guitar. The choice of the instrument came instantly, and to this day, I have no regrets. As the years went by, I dedicated every Saturday morning to that piece of wood, and every note was learned and played with a big smile on my face. As a teenager, I joined a lot of bends, but something did not feel right. I was always troubled by being in the background and doing my thing. When I started college, I also pursued my passion for music which by that time had completely changed. I went from a hardcore rocker to a guy who sheds tears when listening to Son House. The blues is something that I have always cherished and tried to spread amongst my peers. From Muddy Watters and John Lee Hooker to John Mayer and Eric Clapton. I was doing two gigs a week and managed to pay for my education and take a huge load off my parent's backs. Every time I find myself in a stressful situation, I grab the guitar and immediately calm myself down. Even though people think that the door on blues music is closed and that playing in bars is a seasonal thing and a side hustle. I can never truly say that, and if an opportunity comes my way, I will gladly play again. Another possible scenario would be to teach kids how to play acoustic guitar which is something that I have already done on freelance workspaces. Let's face it I guy who is willing to go on stage, play more than a 100 years old blues music without a single singing lesson, can be a great addition to any workforce



# **Health Fitness Specialist**

### Self-employed

Sep 2020 - Sep 2020 (1 month)

After my failed attempt to get into the military, I realized that I could use everything that a learned, fitness and nutrition-wise, to help other people and assist them on their journey. Whether that is muscle building or weight loss. It gets me riled up even writing a description about it, but there are many clickbaits and lies in the fitness community and once I figured what was actually helpful and what was just nonsense, I set out on a mission to prevent people from spending their money and help them follow a sustainable and not to a strict diet. Also, I am a huge advocate of circuit training, and I believe that only bodybuilders and people who aspire to get on stage should do split workouts. Bitola is a city where everyone is training like a bodybuilder, even though most individuals like to be more athletic and not prone to injuries.



### Photographer

Jazz Factory Festival
Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 (3 months)

As a musician on stage, I always wanted a nice picture after every gig to put in my memorabilia. Unfortunately, most of the time, my friends, who, by the way, always had a table in the front row, did not have attention to detail that I had and would take just a couple of photos in which my face would have been blurry. After analyzing every photo, I realized that I had the ability and desire to grab a camera and take pictures of other musicians.

I am glad to say that Saso Popovski is a dear friend of mine who allowed me to be a part of his Jazz Factory Festival and show off my skills. Afterward, Vasil Hadzimanov liked my photos so much that he used them for his upcoming tour banner.

#### Education

# FICT Faculty of Information and Communication Technologies

Diploma of Education, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services

### **Licenses & Certifications**

**Certificate of Completion B2B Copy Crafting** - BizzBee Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2033 cert\_d1k72w6g

**Certificate of Completion B2B Ideal Client Profiling** - BizzBee Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Feb 2023 cert\_4vdcqlm6

**Certificate of Completion B2B Database Creatin** - BizzBee Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2033 cert 2sn1mjkm

**Certificate of Completion B2B Outreach Execution** - BizzBee Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2032 cert\_y8hbnskz

**Certificate of Completion B2B Nurture and Response Handling** - BizzBee

Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2033 cert\_rvgxc8kj

Certificate of Completion B2B Outreach Campaign Optimisation - BizzBee

Solutions

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2033 cert\_wnt2fjdw

in WordPress: SEO - LinkedIn

in Certificate of Completion WordPress:SEO - LinkedIn

Issued Feb 2023 - Expires Dec 2033 AYFj3se5fA3GSpgQfpANWS\_QkbPM

in Software Testing Foundations: Bug Writing and Management - LinkedIn

# **Skills**

Canva • SEO Copywriting • B2B Marketing • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Marketing • Social Media Communications • Organization Skills • Logo Design • Customer Experience • Digital Marketing